[♪♪♪]
[ALARM CLOCK BEEPING]
[HAIR CLIPPERS BUZZING]
[WATCH BEEPS]
MAN 1 [OVER PA]:
Associate to builder services.
WOMAN 1: Right?
MAN 2: Yeah, we'll cut it here.
[SAW BUZZING
AND PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Thought you finished this job
last week.
The owner wants
the driveway wider now.
Heh. When they pay...
They say. Thank you.
MARCUS:
The newer guys take tests.
Like firemen.
Yo, Pops, bet you didn't have
to push dollies at your old job.
Guilty as charged.
[WOMAN 2 SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
How you doing, Jenny?
Mm-hm. Better now.
ROBERT: Ha-ha-ha.
How's it going, Mr. McCall?
All right, Ralphie.
What you got there?
Tuna.
Bread?
Whole-grain, gluten-free.
Okay. Condiments?
Sprouts, avocado
and Vegenaise mayo.
Okay.
There's a bone
in the tuna.
Oh...
What?
Potatoes are a vegetable.
I like crunchy things.
Carrots are crunchy.
Dried seaweed.
I'm a human, not a rabbit.
To make security guard,
you gotta lose weight.
You asked me to help you, but
if you don't apply yourself...
Yeah.
Hey.
Progress, not perfection.
No more chips.
Who needs flavor? Right?
Ha, ha.
[♪♪♪]
[WATCH BEEPS]
[ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
BILLY: All right, see you later.
JAKE: Have a good one, Billy.
[MAKES KISSING NOISES]
Fuck you.
[MEN LAUGH]
ROBERT: Thank you.
JAKE: You're welcome.
He catch that fish yet?
Just hooked it.
TERI:
It's about damn time.
Well, it's a big fish.
Don't know
if he can hang on, though.
Oh, no.
Tooth and nail right now.
Yeah, well,
maybe he's just too old.
[CHUCKLES]
Thought you were gonna
give up refined sugar.
I am.
When?
Any day now.
Yeah?
Bad for your vocal cords.
Body, mind, spirit,
remember?
I bought a little machine
for making demos.
Yeah?
I bet you're good.
What makes you say that?
Intuition.
All right, well,
I'll see you later, Jake.
JAKE:
Okay. See you later, honey.
You let me know what happens
with that, uh, fish.
Okay.
All right, I'll see you.
Hey!
[♪♪♪]
MARCUS:
You'll owe me $100. Watch.
Yo, Pops. We betting on what
you did before you got here.
JAY:
Like, for a living.
I'm saying insurance, claims.
He was a stock dude, man,
on Wall Street.
I was a Pip.
Yo, you were a pimp?
No, not a pimp.
A Pip. P-I-P. Pip.
The fuck is a Pip?
Why you curse so much?
You know, like Gladys Knight
and the Pips. Like this:
Unh.
MAN 1: Check this out!
JAY: Oh, come on!
MARCUS: Stop it.
JENNY:
Yeah. Break it.
MARCUS:
Uh-uh. Don't do that right now.
Oh, the spin?
JAY: What?
Wait a minute.
Gonna blow the whistle? Oh!
Come on. I'm gonna
look it up right now.
Man, I'm looking this up.
[UPBEAT THEME MUSIC
PLAYS ON VIDEO]
Yo, so which one were you?
The one on the right.
MAN 2: Hey, do it again!
Yo, that's not him right there.
Man, that's him with an Afro.
He's bald.
So he had a wig on.
That's gone, yo.
That's him.
♪ Love ♪
♪ Get it ♪
♪ I am sharper than a razor ♪
MAN:
Damn, girl!
Bring it over here now!
TERI:
Hey, Jake. What a fucking night.
JAKE:
Yeah, it's tough
out there, honey.
♪ Too long I've been
Out here on my own ♪
♪ Now I'm about to bring it
Home like a rolling stone ♪
JAKE:
Here you go, kid.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
He ever catch it?
Hm?
The fish.
Oh, yeah. Yes. Yeah, he did.
It's a happy ending.
Well, not exactly.
Old man tied the fish
to the side of the boat,
had to row back to shore,
fish bled in the water,
sharks came
and ate the whole fish
till there was nothing left.
That's just kind of a waste,
isn't it?
No. Depends upon
how you look at it.
The old man met
his greatest adversary
just when he thought
that part of his life was over.
He saw himself
in the fish.
Came to...
Came to respect it
the more it fought.
Why didn't he just
let the fish go?
The old man's
gotta be the old man.
Fish gotta be the fish.
Gotta be who you are
in this world, right?
No matter what.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
♪ I gotta give you
What you love ♪
[RINGTONE PLAYING
ON CELL PHONE]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
MAN [IN RUSSIAN OVER PHONE]:
You've got a client.
[IN RUSSIAN]
I don't want to.
What?
Can't you get someone else?
He wants you.
But this customer
is a pig.
He's waiting outside.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
♪ Take what you love ♪
♪ And when that baby cry
You better look at that baby ♪
How much?
Don't worry about it.
Go make your living.
Thanks, Jake.
♪ But never too much
Baby, take your time ♪♪
[SNIFFLES]
TERI [IN ENGLISH]:
Hey, honey! How you doing?
You ready to have a good time?
ROBERT:
Come on. Pull, pull, pull.
Pull, pull, pull!
Come on, come on.
Eight, seven, six, five,
four, four, four.
Unh!
Oh, come on, now.
Come on.
I can't.
You can't?
What if that were me?
You gonna leave me to die of
smoke inhalation? I'm a buck-90.
How will you pull me
out of a burning building
if you can't
pull a tire 20 yards?
I'm not strong enough.
Don't doubt yourself, son.
Doubt kills. Get up.
Come on. Get up. Get up.
Giddyup, giddyup, giddyup!
On your mark, get set,
pull.
Unh!
Come on. Who's gonna
make security guard?
I am!
Who's gonna make security guard?
Who's gonna make
security guard?
There you go.
I am!
[PANTING]
I like it.
Let's do it again.
[♪♪♪]
[OVER EARBUDS]
♪ All eyes on me
As I'm leaving the scene ♪♪
Loaded with poison,
just like you like it.
Is it your birthday?
No, it was some guy at work.
I didn't want to waste it.
TERI:
Happy birthday,
Some Guy at Work.
How old are you?
Doesn't really matter.
I'm sorry.
I'm breaking protocol, right?
No, no. Listen, hey,
come on, sit down.
Sit. Sit.
Sit.
Okay.
Come on, sit down.
All right.
Sure I'm not
interrupting anything?
Yeah.
So?
I don't know.
You know, I just kind of
felt like a quiet voice.
Before it all goes crazy.
Okay.
I'm Teri.
Bob.
Ow.
That's good.
You know, you don't
look like a Bob.
Oh, yeah? Thank you.
You look like a Robert.
Robert reads books
like this,
and Bob watches TV.
[♪♪♪]
My real name's Alina.
What happened to your face?
Something stupid.
Look, it's not professional.
Just tell me
what you think, okay?
Oh, wow.
Alina the singer.
You and I know what I really am.
I think you can be
anything you wanna be.
Maybe in your world, Robert.
Doesn't really happen
that way in mine.
Change your world.
There's no ring.
Hm?
On your wedding finger,
there's no ring.
No.
No Mrs. Robert at home?
Was there ever?
Once.
Did you break her heart?
She broke mine.
You know, I see
a lot of widowed guys.
Something in your eyes.
You know, it's not sad.
It's just kind of...
lost, you know?
You always read books?
My wife did. She, uh...
She was working through the 100
Books Everybody Should Read.
She made it to 97,
so I figured...
I'd give it a shot.
And one day we'd have
something to talk about
when we get together.
Wow, a hundred books.
Yeah.
Holy moly.
Heh, heh.
How many have you read, Robert?
Ninety-one.
[RINGTONE PLAYING
ON CELL PHONE]
Sorry, this damn thing.
Ninety-one books, though.
You're almost done.
Almost.
What are you gonna do
after that?
Take singing lessons.
Then I'm gonna open
a donut factory.
Heh-heh-heh.
I am. What? Why you laughing?
[BOTH LAUGH]
[♪♪♪]
ALINA:
I love being up at this hour.
ROBERT:
Yeah?
ALINA:
Yeah. You know,
everything's so dark.
It makes everything
seem possible again.
Yeah, me,
I can't sleep at night.
ALINA:
Yeah, well, I get
to hear your stories.
What's your new one about?
Oh, it's about a guy who thinks
he's a knight in shining armor.
The only thing is,
he lives in a world where
knights don't exist anymore.
Kind of sounds like
my world. Heh.
ROBERT:
I'm just up the block.
ALINA:
I'm gonna grab a cab
or something.
Thank you for the quiet voice,
Robert.
You are very welcome,
Alina.
Yeah.
Catch you around, all right?
Good night.
Shit.
See you.
SLAVI [IN RUSSIAN]:
What did you do, huh?
What did you do
to that customer?
[IN RUSSIAN]
Slavi, he hit me.
SLAVI [IN ENGLISH]:
Who do you think you are? Hm?
[IN ENGLISH]
It's all right.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Understand.
It's all right, Robert.
SLAVI:
Let's talk about you
not answering my calls.
Bitch!
[IN RUSSIAN]
Should we give him a card?
[IN ENGLISH]
This girl, she's no good.
Call this number.
I send you another one. Better.
[SLAVI SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Don't be shy. Make the call.
Understand.
[♪♪♪]
JAKE:
Coffee?
MAN:
We need more sugar out here.
[♪♪♪]
I heard she's at the ICU
at Shawmuts.
Someone beat her up real good.
[AMBULANCE SIREN WAILING]
WOMAN [OVER PA]:
Dr. Paley to ICU.
Dr. Paley to ICU, please.
Dr. Mark to the pharmacy.
Dr. Mark to the pharmacy,
please.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[♪♪♪]
Alina.
[MANDY SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[GROANING]
[IN ENGLISH]
Hey, you'll be okay, Alina.
You'll be okay.
[SOBBING]
ROBERT:
Oh. Watch it.
Don't you worry about it.
MANDY: It's okay. It's okay.
Here you go.
I can-- It's fine. Thank you.
Got it.
How's she doing?
Alina. How's she doing?
Who are you?
Just a friend.
A guy hit her.
And she hit him back.
A guy called Slavi.
So Slavi made
example of her.
They do that.
They burned one girl's face
with battery acid.
Keep her around as a reminder
for the rest of us.
They brought Teri over
very young.
Think she got
to the point where
she thought her life
could be hers one day.
Slavi reminded her
it never would be.
He said he'd cut her throat
next time.
He said a whore
who fucks and can't talk
might be worth
twice as much.
[♪♪♪]
ALINA:
You and I know
what I really am.
It's something in your eyes.
ROBERT:
Change your world.
Anything you wanna be.
MANDY:
He said he'd cut her throat
next time.
[SIGHS]
[♪♪♪]
[WOMAN LAUGHING
AND PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
[TECHNO MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Why is that piece of shit
in my parking space?
[CHATTERING IN RUSSIAN]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
BARTENDER:
Hi, Slavi.
[IN ENGLISH] Are they upstairs?
Yes.
[RUSSIAN HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
[MEN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Tevi. You collect
from that fuck, Dmitri?
Yes.
He asked for forgiveness.
Forgiveness?
TEVI:
I told him.
What am I, Jesus Christ?
Ha-ha-ha.
[MEN CONTINUE
SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[IN ENGLISH]
You lost, dedushka?
[IN RUSSIAN]
How did he get up here?
TEVI:
I don't know.
Should I get rid of him?
No.
I'm here for that girl.
You gave me that
a couple of nights ago.
[IN ENGLISH]
We give out lots of cards.
You still can get it up,
dedushka?
[MEN LAUGHING]
I'm here about
a certain girl.
She got beat up
pretty bad.
I'm thinking that maybe you have
wrong address, dedushka.
This girl, she have name?
Her name's Alina.
Alina?
Mm-mm.
Ah...
No, it doesn't ring a bell.
But whoever she is, she must
know how to suck the cock.
[MEN LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
Uh... Okay. Um...
Look, I understand.
These girls that you, uh...
That you represent.
I understand it's like
they're an investment, so, um...
I can give you $9800.
It's cash.
You're wanting to give me $9000?
Ninety-eight hundred. Cash.
For what?
Her freedom.
Uh-huh. Heh, heh.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Can you believe this guy?
[IN ENGLISH]
This guy gonna give me $9000
for one single piece of pussy.
Ah, must be Ferrari pussy.
[MEN LAUGHING]
You fucking Americans think
you can come into my place
and buy whatever you want.
Beautiful Russian girls,
no problem,
just throw down
this bullshit money.
You fucking insult me.
[♪♪♪]
Ha-ha-ha.
I'm just fucking with you, man.
But you got very big balls
coming in here. I like that.
So, $9000
for the troublemaker.
One month.
That's it.
You think
this is one-time payment?
I make this off this girl
in two weeks.
That girl is still child.
I still can sell her
as virgin, huh?
This makes prime earner
for good while.
Take your fucking money
and go back to your house
and jerk off 9800 times.
Then come crawling back here
and talk to me, huh?
She'll be used up
by then for sure.
Maybe then I will let you
have her for nothing. Hm?
[♪♪♪]
Okay.
[MEN LAUGHING]
You're okay, dedushka?
Bye-bye.
You know amerikantsy.
[CHUCKLING]
You forget something?
[MEN CHUCKLING]
[♪♪♪]
Sixteen seconds.
[WATCH BEEPS]
One one-thousand,
two one-thousand,
three one-thousand.
[SCREAMING]
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
Eight one-thousand.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Understand?
[WATCH BEEPS]
Twenty-eight minus 9, 19.
Nineteen.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
Your heart's beating three times
the normal rate.
Because you're losing
so much blood.
About 30 seconds,
your body's gonna shut down
and you're gonna suffocate.
Alina, the girl you beat half
to death, her life will go on.
Yours is gonna end right here,
on this funky floor
over $9800.
[GRUNTING]
You should have taken the money.
Who are you?
Twenty-six one-thousand,
27 one-thousand,
28 one-thousand.
I'm sorry.
[♪♪♪]
[SAW BUZZING]
RALPHIE:
Mr. McCall, it's lunchtime.
Mr. McCall.
Lunchtime.
You test tomorrow, and
you're still eating that?
These are for you.
Open it.
I made the weight.
Tomorrow I'm gonna ace
that test. Thanks to you.
What happened?
Uh...
Hit it on something stupid.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[♪♪♪]
WOMAN [ON TV]:
In what investigators
are calling
a gangland-style execution,
five men were killed
at some point last night
in an office
above this restaurant.
Police sources
have said the killings
have all the earmarks
of a turf war
between rival factions.
Names are not yet
being released--
[AIRPLANE ENGINES WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
MASTERS:
How's it going?
PEDERSON:
How you doing, sir?
Morgan Pederson.
TEDDY:
I know who you are.
Get in the car.
Take me to the murder scene.
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[MAN GROANS]
MASTERS:
We figured two,
maybe three guys
killed them all that quickly.
PEDERSON:
If it was a power play,
no one saw it coming.
None of our informants
heard about this going down.
Security system's drive was
taken so we're blind in here.
At 11:17, a waiter goes up with
a tray of food, finds them dead.
I want images from
every security camera
within a six-block radius.
If you have any trouble,
call that number...
and it will be taken care of.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
Phones charged and on.
I tend to call at odd hours.
Now, if you could drive me
to my residence.
Hey, wait a second,
Mr. Sunshine. Um...
What do I look like to you?
A chauffeur?
This is our town.
You're a fucking guest.
Let me apologize for my conduct.
It was a long flight
on short notice,
and I like to focus,
to work quickly.
The deaths of
Mr. Pushkin's men
have interrupted
his operations here.
Imports, movements of goods,
have all ceased.
That's unacceptable.
I'm the one Mr. Pushkin calls in
when people like you fuck up.
Mm. I don't like your tone--
I'm accountable now.
You have taken
Mr. Pushkin's money for years.
Money that comes
with conditions.
Non-negotiable conditions.
Problem you're having with me is
you think you matter. You don't.
I am all that matters.
And so we're clear:
I'm not here to say "please."
I'm here to tell you what to do.
Be ready for business.
We open tomorrow.
[FORKLIFT BEEPING]
Brian, you seen Ralphie?
Supposed to be taking that
security guard test after work.
Called in and quit.
Quit?
No notice either.
Kids, right?
[♪♪♪]
[LATIN MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
We're closed.
Mr. McCall.
Ralphie.
Heard you quit today.
I got worried.
Uh...
Oh, uh...
My mom had a little
accident here last night.
There was a fire.
ROBERT:
I see.
So I'm gonna help out
around here now.
Okay.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[WOMAN & ROBERT
SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
We have a lot of work to do.
Okay.
Yeah, so--
Need some help?
Yeah, if you're not doing
anything, that'd be awesome.
Helping you.
[LAUGHS]
[♪♪♪]
MASTERS:
Teddy, I checked this out.
the Irish are clean on this one.
They had
nothing to do with it, huh?
You gonna sit down
with all these guys?
I'm telling you.
TEDDY: Yes, I understand.
Duly noted.
[♪♪♪]
MASTERS:
Listen, huh?
Do me a favor, all right?
Whatever you do, don't
call him "Little John," okay?
Frank, why you working
for these fucking Russians?
My money not good enough?
MASTERS:
John, you know
I respect your business.
Mr. Looney, you understand
why I'm compelled
to make this visit.
I don't know shit
about what went down
or who you should be
out looking for.
If I wanna take over anything,
I'd fucking do it.
There'd be nothing left to you.
So maybe you just don't
understand who the fuck I am.
John. Easy, huh?
Don't "easy," Frank.
Shut the fuck up!
Fucking flipperhead.
See, I hate you
fucking Russians.
You're all crazy,
and you're arrogant.
Now, the Irish, we came here for
a piece of the American dream.
You people come over here
to steal it, so fuck all of you.
Well, Mr. Looney,
I appreciate your candor.
It's refreshing
and lets me understand
you're not smart enough
to have done this.
The fuck?
Which brings me
to my next issue.
We pay you 15 percent
to do business here.
The additional 10 percent
you steal, we ignore.
We anticipated it,
as you people are such clichés.
The fact that
you're a rat to the Feds
is also tolerable, Little John.
The fuck?
What we will not tolerate is
getting nothing for our money:
no information, no protection,
no assurances.
You understand, Little Johnny?
Who do you think you are?
Who I am or what I am?
Who I am is complicated. What
I am is easier. I'm a threat.
I alter outcomes.
Throw this motherf-- Unh!
MAN 1 [ON RADIO]:
Whoa, doctor! Call a doctor.
Unbelievable!
It's Napoli in the clutch!
Holy cow!
Oh, fuck!
A tie game. Unbelievable!
That ball was absolutely
massacred by Mike Napoli.
[GRUNTING]
A home run by Napoli.
Boy, can things change.
MAN 2: They certainly can.
This game was over before
this half-inning started.
It is certainly over now!
The final: six to five,
Boston over New York...
[PANTING]
Hey!
Hey! Hey.
This is my town. Do you
understand me? This is my home.
You cannot run around
like a wild animal.
What the fuck was that?
It's a message.
It says, "I'm here."
[♪♪♪]
ROBERT:
What really happened
in there, Ralphie?
Faulty wire or something.
We both know
that's not true.
I'm sorry I wasted your time.
Hey, you didn't waste my time.
My mom doesn't have much
except this place.
And when stuff
like this happens,
I just gotta put everything
on hold for a while
and help her out,
you know?
What was I thinking?
I wasn't gonna pass
the security guard test anyway.
Was there anything
unusually strange
about Slavi
before he was murdered?
Did he mention
a name perhaps?
Agitated
about something?
Slavi never did his business
in front of the girls.
Tevi handled us.
We can't locate
one of the other girls
from Slavi's stable.
Teri.
You know her?
No.
Where we might find her?
No. Sorry.
I didn't know her
that well.
PUSHKIN [ON SPEAKERPHONE]:
Was my message received, Teddy?
TEDDY:
Yes, Mr. Pushkin.
All of our associates--
Irish, Italians, Armenians.
--are all denying any knowledge
or involvement.
We cannot show weakness.
I need this wrapped up quickly.
It will be.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Of course, don't worry.
Good.
[IN ENGLISH]
Now enough of
what you don't know.
Tell me what you do know.
[IN ENGLISH]
Well, I'm still
sifting through things,
but the killings
were spontaneous.
Whoever did this
specialized in killing.
I've rarely seen skills
like this.
I don't think it's someone
we've encountered before.
Whoever it is,
just find him, Teddy.
I'm talking over a million
barrels, this delivery.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Understand?
It will all be well.
[IN ENGLISH]
I'll take care of it.
When you do, be loud about it.
I don't want this
happening again.
[IN RUSSIAN]
Of course.
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
[SIGHS]
Come on.
Stuff it in.
See that?
That son of a bitch.
GILLY: Yeah.
HARRIS: Come on.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
We're closed. Get out.
HARRIS: Let's go.
Time to go.
[GILLY SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
HARRIS:
Nice to see you.
See? You pay on time,
no more problems.
Ha-ha-ha.
All right, let's go.
[IN SPANISH ACCENT]
Mamacita, you need to clean
the grease.
It'll cause a fire.
Good accent.
HARRIS:
See you next week.
GILLY: Let's go get a blowie.
ROBERT: Hey, officers.
HARRIS:
Whoa, put the light down.
What's up?
ROBERT:
I'd like to report a crime.
Really? Call 911.
GILLY:
Let's get out of here.
Fuck that guy.
HARRIS:
Should've shot
that motherfucker.
Take it easy.
How did you get this job?
I blew the commissioner.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
ROBERT [OVER PHONE]:
Why waste city services
when I got two corrupt cops
right in front of me?
It's that guy.
This fucking guy?
Yeah.
Back up.
[♪♪♪]
How'd you get that number?
Wasn't hard.
HARRIS: Yeah?
Neither was this.
HARRIS:
Ask the lady down the street.
The one who had the fire.
Same thing could happen to you
with your whole family inside.
GILLY:
Open it.
HARRIS:
You pay like everybody else.
How many copies?
One.
You must have
a death wish, pal.
What the fuck
do you want, huh? Huh?
Those people
you took the money from,
you should give it back.
Ha-ha-ha. Why would we do that?
That would be in the best
interest of everyone.
Really?
Yeah.
Maybe our best interest
is to tie a block around you
and throw you
in the Mystic, huh?
Let's do that.
It's a good idea.
[♪♪♪]
You're supposed to stand
for something, punk.
Fuck.
Protect and serve.
Uphold the law.
Justice.
Remember?
Who the fuck are you?
ROBERT:
Tomorrow you'll have
returned all the money
you extorted
from those people.
Tell them it will
never happen again.
Do that and this video
will never be seen.
You don't,
and a half an hour later,
you'll watch the uncut version
on every news outlet
in the area.
Now, I'm offering you a chance
to do the right thing. Take it.
That fucking hurt more
than the beating.
[♪♪♪]
RALPHIE:
Mr. McCall. Are you done
standing around or what?
[FOOTSTEPS]
TEDDY:
All the other girls have...
claimed that you were
very close to Teri. Huh?
You lied to me
about that.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
It's pretty.
[SNIFFLING]
When did you last
talk to her?
Over a week ago.
Mm-hm.
I went to the hospital.
Uh, I saw her there.
Did anyone else
visit her?
Yes.
A man.
A man?
Customer?
No.
A nice man.
A black man.
He wanted to know
what happened to her.
His name?
He didn't say.
And your friend, Teri?
No one saw her
after she left hospital.
After what they did to her.
And you contacted her?
No.
No one saw her.
[WHISPERING]
Look at me. Are you
telling me the truth?
You telling me the truth?
The truth?
[WHISPERING]
Yes. Yes.
You telling me the truth?
Yes.
Telling me the truth?
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Yes.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Would you like some water?
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Moisten your throat.
[FAUCET RUNNING]
Thank you.
Sweet.
My angel.
Hm? Yes.
Please. Please.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
So beautiful.
Please, please, Teddy.
Please, Teddy.
But so deceitful.
Please. Please don't.
So fucking deceitful.
Please don't.
You're--
You're hurting me!
Please stop.
[TEDDY GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[DOG BARKING]
[CROWD CHEERING
AND CLAPPING]
MAN 1:
Let's go, Home Mart!
MAN 2: Let's go!
MAN 3: Keep it going, Home Mart!
Here we go. Oh, oh, oh!
I got it! I got it! I got it!
MAN 4: Yeah!
MAN 5: Yeah!
MAN 6:
There you go! Way to go, Bobby!
MAN 7:
There's no place
like Home Mart.
Yeah.
[CHUCKLES]
BOTH:
Oh!
MARCUS: I see you!
JAY: Ralphie, bravo!
JENNY:
You passed your test!
MARCUS:
Looking good, man.
Hey, did they
give you a gun?
[♪♪♪]
PEDERSON:
What the hell
he call us in here for?
MASTERS:
Maybe he's finally done
chasing his own tail.
He needs to go home.
REMAR: Waste of fucking time.
MASTERS:
Yeah, that sounds about right.
I matched the arrival
and departure times
of everyone going in
and out of the restaurant.
I discovered a curious thing.
This person walks
in the front door
several minutes
after Slavi arrived,
but never comes out.
All right. Later. All right.
Thanks.
Jenny, Jenny, Jenny.
Can you do
a quick card refund for me?
Gentleman's in a hurry.
Open that fucking register.
Move, move.
Empty the register. Now.
Go ahead,
open this thing up.
Tell this bitch
to fucking move it.
Open the register up
right now.
Move.
[REGISTER OPENS]
All of it.
Give me all of it.
Come on.
Move, move, move.
That ring too.
Give me that ring.
JENNY: No.
Give me that fucking ring.
JENNY:
Please. It was my mother's.
Fuck your mother.
Give me that ring.
[♪♪♪]
[BOY GIGGLES]
Take it off.
JENNY: It was my mother's.
Shh.
I don't care.
Give me the fucking ring.
JENNY: Please.
ROBERT: It's okay, Jenny.
[♪♪♪]
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
You okay?
Yeah.
Hey, listen. Police said
the guy's done four like this.
Shot a guy over in Somerville
a month ago, so...
It's only money.
[♪♪♪]
You okay?
Hey, Ralphie. Still
a little freaked out.
Well, if you need anything,
let me know.
JENNY:
Thanks, Ralphie.
[♪♪♪]
Oh, my God.
My ring?
[♪♪♪]
[WATCH BEEPS]
Mr. McCall. Sorry to bother you.
Yeah.
We're looking into a homicide
that occurred two weeks ago.
Five dead.
Russian restaurant.
I heard about it on TV.
Happened to be there that night.
Oh, you were?
Yeah.
You wouldn't be here
if I wasn't.
That's right.
We're just checking to see
if any of the patrons
remembered anything suspicious.
Not that I recall.
May I ask why you dined
at that particular restaurant?
I like pirozhki.
There's five Russian restaurants
in walking distance
of your apartment.
I assume they all
serve pirozhki.
Wow. I was meeting a friend.
It was her idea.
Then I guess I should talk--
Sheila Saunders.
But she won't be any help.
She wasn't there.
Her daughter had a fever.
Didn't stay long?
I didn't check my watch.
I see. Well, thanks
for your cooperation.
Very welcome.
Tell me, do you know this girl?
Yeah, I don't know...
I don't remember where from.
What happened?
She fell down
and broke her neck.
Did she?
I'll be in touch.
Don't you wanna leave me
your card, officer?
In case I remember anything?
That's what you policemen
usually do, right?
Must have given them all out.
How'd you find me?
I paid cash. No reservation.
Well, that's what we do,
Mr. McCall.
We who?
We find people we need to find.
[♪♪♪]
[WATCH BEEPS]
Everything about him
is wrong.
[♪♪♪]
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
TEDDY:
And his military history?
No.
Keep digging.
This is what we have
on McCall so far:
College-educated. Works
a straight 40 at the Home Mart.
Bank statements,
tax returns, all jive.
Looks pretty normal.
All lies. Fabricated.
[♪♪♪]
TEDDY:
We need to take him cleanly.
Alive.
A place without cameras,
no witnesses.
[♪♪♪]
A man with his skills,
I want to know who he really is.
I want to know
who he's working for.
MAN:
How you doing?
Give me a coffee, please.
An egg sandwich too. On a roll.
No cheese, please.
JAKE:
You got it.
I'll be back in a minute.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
Is it just you, or are we
waiting for someone else?
I'm sorry. What?
Your hands.
If you really worked
the power lines,
your hands wouldn't
look like that.
We gotta be waiting
for somebody else.
[LAUGHS]
Motherfucker.
[♪♪♪]
Hands where I can see them.
We're gonna take a little walk
across the street. Black Denali.
Here we go.
MASTERS:
What the fuck?
Vary from these instructions
and I'll kill you, understand?
All right.
Stand up.
What the fuck is this?
Masters, let's go.
No witnesses.
MAN:
What's going on out there?
[♪♪♪]
What the fuck?
Let's go.
Shh.
MASTERS:
What the hell is this guy doing?
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
MASTERS:
Remar, you got A side.
Front, follow.
You got C. I got B.
Alive.
MASTERS:
Yeah, yeah, alive. I'm on it.
[♪♪♪]
[TRAIN APPROACHING]
[GRUNTING]
[REMAR GRUNTING]
Motherfucker.
Motherfucker suckered me.
Goddamn it.
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[♪♪♪]
MASTERS:
Shit.
MASTERS [OVER SPEAKER]:
Pederson, check the closets,
the kitchen, the back porch.
PEDERSON:
Closet's empty.
Nothing on the back porch.
REMAR:
Fucking guy.
Lives like a monk.
This guy's got a lot of books.
MASTERS:
Remar, stop fucking around.
Check the computer.
[MONITOR BEEPING]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
MASTERS:
This place is way
too clean, boss.
Something doesn't feel right.
MASTERS:
We've got an empty script.
"Meclizine."
It's used for airsickness.
Travel items purchased
three days ago.
Bought an open-ended plane
ticket to Mexico two days ago.
Leaves Logan 10 a.m. tomorrow.
Guy knew this was coming.
He's on the run.
REMAR:
Get someone at the airport.
TEDDY:
He is not going anywhere.
MASTERS:
What are you talking about?
TEDDY:
He's watching us.
MASTERS:
What do you wanna do?
Find him, or I will
bring people who can.
[♪♪♪]
[BRIAN CHUCKLES]
If you've come for help,
I can't give you any.
I understand.
Do you?
Just came for tea.
Just, uh...
Robert, I have very little
influence these days.
I'm not at the Agency anymore.
I consult on a few things.
That's it.
Susan, I just need to know
who this man is.
[SIGHS]
Who is he to you?
That's why I'm here,
trying to find out.
Tell me what's going on.
Please.
[♪♪♪]
You had a nice funeral,
in case you were wondering.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
You know, when they told Susan
you were dead,
she couldn't comprehend it.
She said,
"Oh, no. Not Robert. Uh-uh.
And not from something
as trivial as a car bomb."
That you're alive
is a big relief.
But it didn't come
as a complete surprise to her.
We used to talk about you
over the years, and she said
if anyone could have
figured a way out,
a way to walk away from it all
for good, you know,
like a real fresh start...
it would have been...
you.
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
SUSAN:
You didn't take out
five pimps, Robert.
You took out the East Coast hub
of Vladimir Pushkin.
ROBERT: Pushkin.
Mm-hm.
He's similar
to the other oligarchs
who jumped in bed
with the Russian mafia,
only he funds everything:
gasoline, weapons,
girls, you name it.
He's built an intricate
network on both U.S. coasts
that are incredibly
well-insulated.
His money and political ties
make him untouchable.
Your friend here is who Pushkin
sends when he's got a problem.
Teddy Rensen.
Real name, Nicolai Itchenko.
Skill set honed in Spetsnaz.
He's formidable and smart.
Ran a wing of the secret
police for years.
Went private
when the Union fell.
Basically, he's a sociopath
with a business card.
ROBERT:
Mm.
Thank you, darling.
You know these two?
Uh...
Boston P.D. Probably on
Pushkin's payroll, I assume.
Three years. Detective Remar
and Detective Pederson.
Only now they're dead.
They found them yesterday
in the trunk of their car
in the precinct parking lot.
Suffocated. Testicles blown off
and shoved down their throats.
Classic Russian mob hit.
Teddy's work.
Third one,
Detective Masters
hasn't shown up for work
in several days.
Robert, I don't have
to tell you what happens next.
He won't stop
until he kills you
and anyone you care about.
[♪♪♪]
SUSAN:
Didn't sleep a wink, did you?
Hey.
Mm.
Robert, that girl,
Alina...
Why?
I couldn't tell you
why it mattered.
Why what they did to her,
that mattered to me so much.
One day somebody does
something unspeakable
to someone else to...
someone you hardly knew,
and you...
do something about it
because you can.
Mm.
Because it's who you are? Hm?
Who you've always been?
Sometimes we make
the wrong choices
to get to the right place.
Mm.
I know a part of you died
when Vivian did.
But not the part
she loved the most.
[♪♪♪]
Go be him.
[CHUCKLES]
Yep.
Don't forget
to say goodbye.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
Goodbye.
BRIAN:
Everything all right?
Were you able to help him?
He didn't come for help.
He came for permission.
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
[CAR ALARM WAILING]
[♪♪♪]
Fuck.
[ALARM CONTINUES WAILING]
What the fuck?
[ALARM CHIRPS
THEN STOPS WAILING]
[REMOTE BEEPS
THEN ENGINE STARTS]
[REMOTE BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
Testing one, two, three, four.
[REMOTE BEEPS]
[GASPING]
Pushkin.
I need to know everything:
who, what, when, where, why.
Before you tell me
you're not gonna talk...
[REMOTE BEEPS]
You can go fuck yourself,
you know that?
[COUGHING]
[REMOTE BEEPS]
[GASPING]
You're gonna give me
what I need.
Or not.
You're such a fuck.
Why don't you
get out of here
and go fuck yourself,
you fucking motherfucker?
You know who you're
dealing with, huh?
I am a cop, you moron!
I swear to God,
I'll fuck--
[COUGHING]
Okay. Open it.
Open the fucking wind--
Huh?
I'm Boston P.D.
I don't have a lot of time.
Which means
you don't have any.
Look, you are in
a lot of trouble.
Just let me go.
I'm gonna let you go.
I'll be back.
No!
Motherfucker! Wait.
Wait!
We're here to see Andri.
[DOOR BUZZING]
[CHATTERING]
[MAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER PA]
[MEN SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
MASTERS:
Hey, Andri. Listen, this
location's been compromised.
Get all your shit out of here.
You gotta truck it all out.
The fuck
I'm going to do that.
And who's this fucking
piece of shit?
Pushkin made the call.
I'm just the new guy.
Pushkin.
Pushkin. I--
Pushkin's money. What the fuck
you give a fuck, Andri, huh?
[♪♪♪]
Is that a Heckler Koch?
This?
ROBERT: Yeah.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
What is he saying?
I don't fucking...
Can I see it?
Oh, you want to see my gun?
Uh, yes and no.
No.
MASTERS: Oh, fuck!
All right, all right, all right!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
You're so fucking nuts!
Fuck!
All right.
Everybody settle down.
Frank tells me
you're the man, Andri. Yeah?
He says your guys
are incredibly loyal toward you.
If you tell them
to put their guns down,
lay down on the floor,
they'll do that, won't they?
Indulge me, Andri.
Tell them to lay down.
ROBERT:
There you go.
Thank you very much.
There you go. Mr. Pushkin
thanks you very much.
We're going out of business.
Closing down shop.
Mr. Pushkin thanks you
very much. There you are.
Here you go.
You're welcome.
Accept these parting gifts
on behalf of Mr. Pushkin.
There you go.
Three, two-- Look at that,
perfect. --one.
Thank you.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Right around to the right.
Call it in.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]: Boston P.D.
Detective Frank Masters.
I am 10-13 at 155 Warren Street,
rear entrance.
Repeat: Detective Frank Masters,
10-13,
155 Warren Street,
rear entrance.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Anything else I can do for you?
You tell me, Frank.
I know you got an escape plan.
Where do you keep it?
Heh. Yeah? What's
your escape plan, huh?
Not about me. It's about you.
Where do you keep it?
Fuck you, you motherfucker.
You have fucked me
so fucking bad!
You did this!
Do you hear yourself?
You did it to this badge,
Frank.
You disrespected this badge.
You understand me?
Fuck you,
you motherfucker.
I got nothing, all right?
You hear me?
I got nothing
because of you!
You think they're not coming for
you, you're not fucking next?
I am a fucking dead man!
Do something about it.
You don't know
who these people are!
I'm a fucking dead man.
I won't last a fucking week.
Then do the right thing.
Motherfu--
[SIGHS]
Do the right thing, Frank.
Police officer
for 22 years,
I know you didn't get this far
and not have an out.
Where do you keep it?
I was a fucking good cop.
[POLICE SIRENS
WAILING IN DISTANCE]
I was.
I understand.
Do the right thing.
Do it for the good cops,
Frank.
Where do you keep it?
[♪♪♪]
Just let me know when
you're done, detective.
[SIREN WAILING]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
MAN 1:
This guy here.
He was cuffed
to the pipes back here,
200,000 in the trunk
of his car.
Recording of the whole deal
with these guys on the seat.
Crazy. And that was tacked
to his jacket.
That's not the best part.
MAN 2:
We're on scene for the duration.
MAN 3:
Get IDs on all those guys.
Check this out.
[♪♪♪]
AGENT 1:
Holy shit!
AGENT 2:
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
AGENT 1:
Who's gonna fucking count this?
MAN [IN RUSSIAN OVER PHONE]:
We've searched the city.
No sign of him.
McCall has disappeared.
Mr. Pushkin
has been notified.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
My men will find him.
Good.
[NECK CRACKING]
I got to piss.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
[♪♪♪]
ROBERT:
He's not coming back.
Had enough?
You certainly have my attention.
Because I can keep going.
Brick by brick.
Dollar by dollar.
Body by body.
Or you can call your boss
and tell him to shut down
his operation.
Tonight.
That's not much of an offer.
Only one you're gonna get.
When you pray for rain,
you gotta deal with the mud too.
When you look at me...
what do you see?
[CHUCKLES]
Hm?
The answer's nothing.
I have no feelings about you
one way or the other.
You're like...
Like lint or a bottle cap.
You're just a thing to remove.
I knew a Russian police captain
back in the day.
He told me about
a case he worked on.
Can't remember
the guy's name.
He was a famous scholar,
lived in Moscow.
He was a humanitarian,
an author.
Anyway, he decided
to share his abundance
with someone less fortunate.
And even though
he had five children,
he opened his home to a sixth.
An orphan,
12-year-old boy.
Kid had been pounded
by the system from an early age.
Troubled.
Prone to violence.
A lost cause.
Stop me if you know this one.
Oh, no. Carry on.
Okay. So this good man
opened his home to this boy.
And when the boy stole from him,
this good man loved him anyway.
When the boy
failed in school,
this man showed
understanding and patience.
When the boy lied and cheated
and clawed and fought,
this good man showed
compassion and love
until the boy,
who had never felt
anything like being
wanted or loved,
he finally did.
The man had broken through.
It was a miracle.
One week later, intruders
broke into the man's house.
Killed the man
and his wife in bed.
They said some small things
were stolen,
things a child might steal.
No one knows for sure.
The man's children
were sent off to relatives.
The boy, the orphan,
shipped back to hell.
Just when he finally
had a chance at life,
it was snatched away
by two bullets.
It's a well-known story.
Mm. They ever catch who did it?
Did they?
Maybe they didn't look
in the right place.
Sometimes the answer's
in front of you.
[IN RUSSIAN]
I think the boy killed them.
[IN ENGLISH]
I think the boy did it.
The boy was scared his foster
parents would wake up one day
and realize he wasn't worth it,
like all the others had.
And he couldn't bear
the thought
that this good man
would do that to him.
Would throw him away
like a piece of lint
or a bottle cap.
So...
he decided
not to find out.
What do you think,
Nicolai?
You think you know me?
[CHUCKLES]
You strike me as
a sentimental man, Mr. McCall.
That's surprising.
I...
I don't possess that chip.
I never could understand
what comes from feeling that way
except weakness.
The men I killed,
your men,
I gave them a chance.
They made their decision.
I'm giving you
the opportunity to make yours.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
You let me know
when you decide.
Of course.
I've done some bad things
in my life, Nicolai.
Things I'm not proud of.
I promised someone
that I love very much
that I would never go back
to being that person.
But for you,
I'm gonna make an exception.
You asked me what I saw
when I looked at you.
What do you see
when you look at me?
[♪♪♪]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PHONE LINE RINGING]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
FBI.
How can I direct your call?
Agent Mosley, please.
MOSLEY:
Agent Mosley.
Heard you found
some money today.
Who is this?
Concerned citizen.
Check your personal e-mail.
Make sure you're
sitting down when you do.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
[WATCH BEEPS]
PUSHKIN [OVER PHONE]:
He hit my tankers.
And you tell me not to worry?
That you'll
take care of things?
Only I've been
further embarrassed.
NICOLAI:
I have a new team.
It's simply a matter of time.
[IN RUSSIAN]
You're out of time.
[IN ENGLISH]
New York had to shut down.
Nothing is moving.
My calls
aren't being answered.
I've lost tens of millions
today alone.
[IN RUSSIAN]
It will all be well.
Stop the bleeding
or don't come back.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
Go fuck yourself.
[♪♪♪]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yes?
[IN ENGLISH] Mr. McCall.
Nicolai.
Your life for theirs.
Whose?
[LINE BEEPS]
You'll want to answer that.
[KEYPAD BEEPS]
Yes?
Mr. McCall?
Ralphie?
They came into the store.
Who's with you?
Jenny, Brian, Jay and Marcus.
What's going on? Wait--
Oh, my God.
No.
[LINE BEEPS]
My men there will kill them
in 30 minutes.
Unless you're here in 29.
You know the place.
You can still smell
the burning gasoline.
[LINE BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
NICOLAI [IN RUSSIAN]:
He's close. Get ready.
MAN 1 [IN RUSSIAN]:
Here comes the bus.
NICOLAI [IN ENGLISH]:
Just checking on you,
sentimental man.
ROBERT [OVER PHONE]:
Yeah?
You willing to die
for your friends?
Are you?
NICOLAI [OVER PHONE]:
When you see him, shoot him.
[MAN 1 SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
MAN 1 [IN RUSSIAN]:
The bus is empty.
[♪♪♪]
NICOLAI [IN RUSSIAN]:
Kill one.
MAN 2 [IN RUSSIAN]:
Kill one of them.
MAN 3 [IN RUSSIAN]:
You wanna be first?
[SOFT POP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER PA]
MAN 4:
Where is that coming from?
I don't know.
[MAN 4 SHOUTS IN RUSSIAN]
I don't know!
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
JAY:
They're gonna kill Ralphie, yo.
MARCUS:
They're gonna fucking kill him.
♪ Too much for the man ♪
♪ He couldn't make it ♪
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
Which way?
What?
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
The song. Which way
is it coming from?
The P.A. system's
in the security office.
Stand! Now.
♪ Ooh, what's left
Of his world ♪
♪ The world he left behind ♪
♪ Not so long-- ♪♪
[MUSIC STOPS]
[♪♪♪]
[NECK SNAPS THEN BODY THUDS]
RALPHIE:
Mr. McCall? What's going on?
Who are these people?
[LOCK CLICKS]
ROBERT [OVER RADIO IN RUSSIAN]:
Come here quickly!
I need your help.
[SPEAKS IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Report. Where are you?
[SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN]
RALPHIE:
Don't shoot. Don't shoot.
I--
I can't understand you.
Okay, I'm going down.
[IN ENGLISH] Get down!
ROBERT:
Psst!
Ralphie.
Get everybody out of here.
Don't leave anybody behind.
You use the service doors
in the back. Okay? Go.
[KEYPAD BEEPS
THEN LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Yeah?
Very clever, Mr. McCall.
I've decided to come
and see you.
Yeah?
I'll be waiting for you.
[♪♪♪]
NICOLAI:
Find the hostages.
[DOORS BEEPING]
[SCOPE POWERING UP]
♪ Before I die alone ♪
♪ Let me have vengeance ♪
♪ I will have vengeance ♪
♪ Before I die alone ♪
♪ Let me have vengeance ♪
♪ I will have vengeance ♪
[CHOKING]
♪ Before I die alone ♪
♪ Before my time has gone ♪
♪ There's just one thing
I have to do ♪
[GRUNTING]
♪ Before the fire and stone ♪
♪ Before your world has gone ♪
♪ Have you some patience ♪
♪ 'Cause I will have
My vengeance ♪
♪ Before I die alone ♪
♪ Let me have vengeance ♪
♪ Before my time has gone ♪
♪ I will have vengeance ♪
♪ Before I die alone ♪
♪ Let me have vengeance ♪
♪ Before my time has gone ♪
♪ I will have vengeance ♪
[GRUNTS]
[GAS HISSING]
[DRILL WHIRRING]
♪ Before I die alone ♪
♪ Before my time has gone ♪
♪ Let me have vengeance ♪
♪ I will, I will ♪
♪ I will have vengeance ♪
♪ I will have vengeance ♪♪
[CLINKING]
[♪♪♪]
[CLATTERING]
[YELLS]
[YELLING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[SCREAMS]
It's me, Mr. McCall.
It's Ralphie.
[RALPHIE GRUNTING]
You said not to leave
anybody behind.
Buck-ninety, my ass.
[♪♪♪]
RALPHIE:
Come on.
Aah! Oh, fuck! Unh.
[GUNFIRE]
You all right?
Aah. I've been shot.
Can you walk?
Yeah.
I'm gonna need you
to do something. Look at me.
Ralphie, focus. Focus.
Okay.
Can you make it
to the breaker box?
[GUNSHOT]
Forty seconds, exactly.
Forty seconds exactly.
[GUNFIRE]
[WATCH BEEPS]
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING AND GRUNTING]
[RALPHIE GRUNTING]
[CLATTERING]
[GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[RALPHIE GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
[FIRE ALARM BUZZING]
Shit.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANING]
[NAIL GUN FIRES]
Who are you?!
[♪♪♪]
[NAIL GUN CLATTERS]
Shit. Oh, shit.
[♪♪♪]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING
IN DISTANCE]
[SHOWER RUNNING]
[♪♪♪]
ROBERT:
I'd stay in there if I were you.
Who are you?
Everybody wants to know.
Gun's not there.
Just put the towel on.
What do you want?
I want the head
of the snake.
[CHUCKLES]
So it's you.
And now you've come to kill me.
Yes.
And tell me,
what do you gain from my death?
Peace.
Peace is expensive to buy.
But I can purchase it
for you.
What is your price?
Are you there?
[FAUCET RUNNING]
[♪♪♪]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Guards, guards!
[PUSHKIN SCREAMING]
[♪♪♪]
ALINA:
Hey!
Hey! Hey, Robert.
Hey.
I remembered
you lived around here,
so I've been swinging by
the last few days.
ROBERT:
Yeah?
Yeah.
Pretty different, huh?
Night and day.
Yeah, well...
I get my stitches out
next week.
Um...
I'm reading now.
Oh, no.
Yeah. I know.
Very good.
I got it
from a used book store.
The guy there recommended it
to me. It's good.
I got a job too.
A real job with real hours
and stuff.
Okay.
[♪♪♪]
You know, when they gave me
my stuff back at the hospital,
there was this envelope
with my name on it.
Almost $10,000 inside
and a ticket out of town.
Probably hush money, right?
Probably.
Who cares?
A new start.
Alina the singer.
Someone once told me I could be
whoever I wanted to be.
Body, mind...
Spirit.
I'm gonna miss
your stories, Robert.
You got your own now.
Thank you.
For everything.
[SIGHS]
I'll catch you around.
Okay.
Bye, Robert.
Goodbye, Alina.
[♪♪♪]
♪ A change of scenes ♪
♪ A change of style ♪
♪ A change of hopes ♪
♪ With no regrets ♪
♪ A chance to watch ♪
♪ Admire the distance ♪
♪ Still occupied ♪
♪ Though you forget ♪
♪ Different colors
Different shades ♪
♪ Over each
Mistakes were made ♪
♪ I took the blame ♪
♪ Directionless
So plain to see ♪
♪ A loaded gun
Won't set you free ♪
♪ So you say ♪
♪ Feels like a close
It's coming to ♪
♪ Fuck am I gonna do? ♪
♪ It's too late
To start over ♪
♪ This is the only thing I--
Thing I know ♪
♪ Sometimes I feel
Like all I ever do is ♪
♪ Find different ways
To word the same old songs ♪
♪ Ever since I came along ♪
♪ From the day
"Hi, My Name Is" dropped ♪
♪ Started thinking
My name was "fault" ♪
♪ 'Cause any time
Things went wrong ♪
♪ I was the one
They would blame it on ♪
♪ The media made me
The equivalent ♪
♪ Of a modern-day
Genghis Khan ♪
♪ Tried to argue it was
Only entertainment, dog ♪
♪ Gangsta? No
Courageous balls ♪
♪ Had to change my style
Said I'm way too soft ♪
♪ And I sound like AZ and Nas
Out came the claws ♪
♪ And the fangs
Been out since then ♪
♪ But until the instant
I went against it ♪
♪ It was ingrained in me ♪
♪ I wouldn't amount
To a shit-stain, I thought ♪
♪ Had to unlearn everything
My brain was taught ♪
♪ Do I belong in this game?
Just wanna play my part ♪
♪ Should I make waves
Or not? ♪
♪ So in my brain
The tug of war wages on ♪
♪ And I don't wanna
Seem ungrateful ♪
♪ Or disrespect the art form
I was raised upon ♪
♪ But sometimes
You gotta take a loss ♪
♪ And have people
Rub it in your face ♪
♪ Before you get made
Pissed off ♪
♪ And keep plugging
It's your only outlet ♪
♪ And your only outfit
They're gonna talk about it ♪
♪ Better find a way to
Counter it quick and make it ♪
♪ Feel like I've said this
A kabillion-eighty times ♪
♪ How many times can I say
The same thing ♪
♪ Different ways that rhyme?
What I really wanna say is ♪
♪ If there's anyone
That can relate to my story ♪
♪ Bet you feel the same way
When I was in the same place ♪
♪ When I was afraid to ♪
♪ I was afraid to make
A single sound ♪
♪ Afraid I would never
Find a way out ♪
♪ Afraid I'd never be found ♪
♪ I don't wanna go
Another round ♪
♪ An angry man's power
Will shut you up ♪
♪ Trip wires fill this house
With tip-toed love ♪
♪ Run out of excuses
For everyone ♪
♪ So here I am
And I will not run ♪
♪ Guts over fear ♪
♪ The time is near ♪
♪ I shed a tear ♪
♪ For all the times
I let you push me around ♪
♪ And let you keep me down ♪
♪ Now I got guts over fear
Guts over fear ♪
♪ Feels like a close
It's coming to ♪
♪ Fuck am I gonna do? ♪
♪ It's too late
To start over ♪
♪ This is the only thing I--
Thing I know ♪
♪ I know what it's like
I was there once ♪
♪ Single parents
Hate your appearance ♪
♪ Did you struggle
To find your place? ♪
♪ And the pain spawns
All the anger on ♪
♪ Wasn't till
I put the pain in songs ♪
♪ Learned
Who to aim it on ♪
♪ That I made a spark
Started to spit hard as shit ♪
♪ Learned how to harness it
While the reins were off ♪
♪ A lot of bizarre shit
But the crazy part ♪
♪ Soon as I stopped saying
I gave a fuck ♪
♪ Haters started
To appreciate my art ♪
♪ And it just breaks my heart
All the pain I caused ♪
♪ What am I gonna do
When the rage is gone? ♪
♪ And the lights go out
In that trailer park? ♪
♪ The window is closing
Nowhere I can go with flows ♪
♪ Frozen 'cause there's no
Emotion for me to pull from ♪
♪ A bunch of playful songs
I make for fun ♪
♪ So to the break of dawn
I go recycling the same song ♪
♪ But I'd rather make
"Not Afraid 2" ♪
♪ Than make another
"We Made You" ♪
♪ I don't wanna seem
Indulgent ♪
♪ When I discuss my lows
And my highs ♪
♪ My demise and my uprise
Pray to God ♪
♪ I just opened enough eyes
Later on ♪
♪ Gave you the supplies
And the tools ♪
♪ To hopefully use it
To make you strong ♪
♪ Lift yourself up
When you feel like I felt ♪
♪ 'Cause I can't explain
How exhausted my legs felt ♪
♪ Just having to balance
My dang self ♪
♪ When on eggshells
I was made to walk ♪
♪ Thank you, Ma
'Cause that gave me ♪
♪ The strength
to cause Shady-mania ♪
♪ So when they empty
That stadium ♪
♪ I made it out of that house
Found a place in this world ♪
♪ When the day was done
So this is for every kid ♪
♪ Who all's they ever did
Was dreamt ♪
♪ Of one day
Just getting accepted ♪
♪ I represent
Anyone similar ♪
♪ You are the reason
That I made this song ♪
♪ And everything
You're scared to say
♪ Don't be afraid
To say no more ♪
♪ From this day forward
Let them A-holes talk ♪
♪ Take it
With a grain of salt ♪
♪ And eat
Their fucking faces off ♪
♪ The legend
Of the angry blond ♪
♪ Lives on through you
When I'm gone ♪
♪ To think I was gone ♪
♪ Afraid
To make a single sound ♪
♪ Afraid I would never
Find a way out ♪
♪ Afraid I'd never be found ♪
♪ I don't wanna go
Another round ♪
♪ An angry man's power
Will shut you up ♪
♪ Trip wires fill this house
With tip-toed love ♪
♪ Run out of excuses
For everyone ♪
♪ So here I am
And I will not run ♪
♪ Guts over fear ♪
♪ The time is near ♪
♪ I shed a tear ♪